The world is here.
One world, one game, we're all the same.
Hear the whole planet scream the name.
Raise your hands up high.
We're dancing till the final whistle cries
From Brazil to France, watch the samba and the play
Argentina, Germany, Spain
Champions everywhere
England, Portugal
The Roars getting loud
Mexico, Canada, USA
making us proud
Ole, Ole, Ole
Sing it loud
For the crowd
Ole, Ole, Ole
One world, one game
We're all the same
Hear the whole planet
Scream the name
Oh, raise your hands up high
We're dancing till the final whistle cry
Japan and Morocco, the underdogs rise
Cape Verde dreaming on the brand new skies
Croatian Netherlands, the battles on the green
Every flag is flying for the title of our king
Hands up for the world tonight
Sing loud, let the colors unite
One ball, one dream, one beating heart
This is the moment, let the party start
One world, one game, we're all the same
Hear the whole planet scream the name
Oh, raise your hands up high
We're dancing till the final whistle cry
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
20, 26, we are one!